[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what European country did the first modern perfume originate in 1370?", "correct_answer": "Hungary", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Poland", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Sun was once regarded as a small and insignificant star, but is now believed to be brighter than approximately 85% of the stars in the galaxy.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first person to parachute?", "correct_answer": "Andres-Jacques Garnerin", "incorrect_answers": ["Leonardo Da Vinci", "Lino LaCedelli", "David Gaithier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tequila is named after a town with the same name in the country where it is a traditional drink.", "correct_answer": "Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Chile", "Spain", "Portugal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This simple but powerful bomb made out of a gas filled bottle was named after a Soviet politician and diplomat.", "correct_answer": "A Molotov cocktail", "incorrect_answers": ["A Khrushchev cocktail", "A Lenin bomb", "A Kerensky  surprise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this year massage therapy and bodywork were officially offered for the first time as a basic medical service, in Atlanta, GA.", "correct_answer": "1996", "incorrect_answers": ["1990", "1999", "1987"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A unique property of water is that its solid form, ice, does not sink as may be expected, but floats. What is the reason for this phenomenon?", "correct_answer": "Lower density of ice compared to liquid water", "incorrect_answers": ["The specific resistance of water to solids", "Temperature differences between the solid and liquid forms", "Lower volume of ice compared to liquid water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Water is divided into soft and hard, depending on its chemical composition. Hard water washes soap from your hands faster, because of its high contents of what?", "correct_answer": "Minerals", "incorrect_answers": ["Polar molecules", "Free electrons", "Salts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these countries was foot binding practiced?", "correct_answer": "China", "incorrect_answers": ["Vietnam", "India", "Peru"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Orange is considered a safety color.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Carl Albert High School was named after Carl Bert Albert, who was the Speaker of the House of Representatives from 1971 to 1977. What small Oklahoma town did he hail from?", "correct_answer": "Bugtussle", "incorrect_answers": ["Enid", "Bushyhead", "Slaughterville"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In December, 1968, the corpse of an alleged Bigfoot, encased in a block of ice was examined by cryptozoologists. What was the name given to the specimen in the ice?", "correct_answer": "The Minnesota Iceman", "incorrect_answers": ["Snow Gnome", "The caveman", "Chilly Will"]}]